

MIKAEL LE GAL

CONTACT

(+34) 619 95 86 58 legal.mikael@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a creative, detail-oriented person with a passion for everything related to design and learning. My experience as a freelancer has allowed me to develop excellent problem-solving skills and the ability to work independently, but I am still a team player at heart.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2020 Högskolan i Skövde

Master's Degree in Informatics. Composed of two Magister's programmes: Serious Games, and Digital Narrative, Games and Cultural Heritage.

2006 - 2011 University of Alicante

Architectural Technologist. Bachelor's degree on construction and structure engineering specialized in the areas of Project Management, Construction Management and Patrimony Intervention.

2014 - 2019 **Digital Artist**Freelance extra job working as illustrator

Freelance extra job working as illustrator or graphic designer for several clients, producing graphical elements such as festival posters, album covers, corporate videos and more.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2011 - 2018 Private Tutor

Freelance job working as a private tutor in the subjects of Mathematics, Physics, Arts and English to children from 5 to 18 years old. In Alicante, San Vicente, and San Juan; Spain.

Working for YMCA Hayo-Went-Ha Camp organizing activities and taking care of a small group of children at a camp and during camping trips. In Michigan, USA.

2010 -2010 Private Tutor

Working for Know-How S.L. as a tutor in subjects such as Mathematics, Physics, Biology and Technical Drawing for small groups of high school children. In San Juan, Spain.

2007 - 2007 Store Clerk

Working for Alcampo S.A. restocking and maintaining a section of a supermarket and providing customer service. In Alicante, Spain.

SKILLS NONE FUNDAMENTAL BASIC INTERMEDIATE ADVANT Unity C# HTML CSS JavaScript React Git Photoshop Illustrator Clip Studio Paint Blender ZBrush LANGUAGES

Spanish



English



Swedish



HOBBIES

Painting digitally, listening to music and playing video games are among my favourite indoors activities. When I want to enjoy my time outside I go running or hiking, or I have a nice coffee with good company.